<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="_0_0">0.0</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_alt_shortcut_label">Alt+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_ctrl_shortcut_label">Ctrl+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_delete_shortcut_label">delete</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_enter_shortcut_label">enter</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_function_shortcut_label">Function+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_meta_shortcut_label">Meta+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_shift_shortcut_label">Shift+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_space_shortcut_label">space</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_sym_shortcut_label">Sym+</string>
    <string name="abc_prepend_shortcut_label">Menu+</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="about_coinbase_wallet">About Coinbase Wallet</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="accessibility_fingerprint_dialog_help_area">Help message area</string>
    <string name="action_existing_user_backup_desc">"You can now securely backup your Coinbase Wallet's private keys to Google Drive"</string>
    <string name="action_existing_user_backup_title">Introducing Drive backup</string>
    <string name="action_hooray_desc">Why not leave us a rating on the Play Store?</string>
    <string name="action_hooray_title">Hooray!</string>
    <string name="action_mind_telling_us_desc">Your feedback helps us improve. We want to make the app better for you.</string>
    <string name="action_mind_telling_us_title">Mind telling us why?</string>
    <string name="action_new_user_backup_desc">If you lose your recovery phrase you will not be able access your wallet</string>
    <string name="action_new_user_backup_title">Back up recovery phrase</string>
    <string name="action_rate_app_title">Enjoying Coinbase Wallet?</string>
    <string name="activate_secure_lock_screen">Please activate secure lock screen from settings</string>
    <string name="active_network">Default network</string>
    <string name="active_wallet">Active wallet</string>
    <string name="active_wallet_name">Wallet %d</string>
    <string name="add_any_erc20_token">Add any ERC20 Token</string>
    <string name="add_payment_method">Add a payment method</string>
    <string name="add_to_bookmarks">Add to Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="add_verify_payment_methods">Add or verify payment methods</string>
    <string name="added_to_bookmarks">%s added to Bookmarks.</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="address_copied">Address copied</string>
    <string name="address_hint">Address…</string>
    <string name="address_not_found_alert_body">No valid address was found for this user</string>
    <string name="address_not_found_alert_title">Oops!</string>
    <string name="adjust_miner_fee">Choose speed</string>
    <string name="adjust_miner_fee_sub_header">Estimated time for price range</string>
    <string name="advanced_title">Advanced</string>
    <string name="airdrop_action_item">Tap to claim</string>
    <string name="airdrop_description">From Uniswap &amp; 1Inch</string>
    <string name="airdrop_modal">Airdrops</string>
    <string name="airdrop_title">Claim Airdrop</string>
    <string name="alert_description">Alert</string>
    <string name="already_done_this">I’ve already done this</string>
    <string name="already_have_wallet">I already have a wallet</string>
    <string name="amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="amount1">First amount</string>
    <string name="amount2">Second amount</string>
    <string name="annual_interest">Annual Interest</string>
    <string name="apache_v2_license">" Apache License Version 2.0, January 2004 http://www.apache.org/licenses/ TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION 1. Definitions. License shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document. Licensor shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License. Legal Entity shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition, control means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity. You (or Your) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising permissions granted by this License. Source form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications, including but not limited to software source code, documentation source, and configuration files. Object form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions to other media types. Work shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work (an example is provided in the Appendix below). Derivative Works shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative Works thereof. Contribution shall mean any work of authorship, including the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, submitted means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing by the copyright owner as Not a Contribution. Contributor shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work. 2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form. 3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s) with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You institute patent litigation against any entity (including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate as of the date such litigation is filed. 4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You meet the following conditions: (a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative Works a copy of this License; and (b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices stating that You changed the files; and (c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and (d) If the Work includes a NOTICE text file as part of its distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed as modifying the License. You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use, reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with the conditions stated in this License. 5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise, any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of this License, without any additional terms or conditions. Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions. 6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file. 7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each Contributor provides its Contributions) on an AS IS BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License. 8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory, whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise, unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages. 9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability. END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS APPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work. To apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following boilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets [] replaced with your own identifying information. (Don't include the brackets!) The text should be enclosed in the appropriate comment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a file or class name and description of purpose be included on the same printed page as the copyright notice for easier identification within third-party archives. Copyright [yyyy] [name of copyright owner] Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the License); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an AS IS BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License. "</string>
    <string name="app_name">Wallet</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="apr">APR</string>
    <string name="authentication_switching_error_message">Something went wrong and we were notified. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="authentication_switching_error_title">Unable to switch authentication methods</string>
    <string name="authentication_title">Choose lock method</string>
    <string name="available">Available</string>
    <string name="available_payment_method_1_fields">%1$s</string>
    <string name="available_payment_method_2_fields">%1$s • %2$s</string>
    <string name="available_payment_method_3_fields">%1$s • %2$s • %3$s</string>
    <string name="back_up_manually">Back up manually</string>
    <string name="back_up_now">Back up now</string>
    <string name="back_up_on_google_drive">Back up on Google Drive</string>
    <string name="backup_now">Back up now</string>
    <string name="backup_phrase">Recovery phrase</string>
    <string name="backup_text_body">You will be shown a secret recovery phrase on the next screen. The recovery phrase is the only key to your wallet. It will allow you to recover access to your wallet if your phone is lost or stolen.</string>
    <string name="backup_unable_to_access_account">I understand that if I lose my recovery phrase, I will not be able to access my account.</string>
    <string name="backup_your_wallet">Back up your wallet</string>
    <string name="balance_not_enough_to_cover_fee">Insufficient balance to fund the network fee required by this transfer</string>
    <string name="banned_location_dialog_recover_message">To recover your funds, please copy the 12 word recovery phrase and import it to another wallet product that works in your region.</string>
    <string name="banned_location_dialog_restore_message">If you backed up your 12 word recovery phrase to Google Drive, you can access your recovery phrase by restoring your wallet</string>
    <string name="banned_location_dialog_title">Wallet is not supported in your region</string>
    <string name="be_extra_safe_manual_backup">Be extra safe, and also back up manually</string>
    <string name="biometric">Biometric</string>
    <string name="biometric_protection">Biometric Change Protection</string>
    <string name="biometric_protection_footer">Leaving this disabled will let you confirm transactions even if you change your fingerprint or face authentication</string>
    <string name="blank" />
    <string name="bottom_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.bottomsheet.BottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="button_description">Button</string>
    <string name="buy">Buy</string>
    <string name="buy_canceled">An error occurred, please try again</string>
    <string name="buy_status">Buy status %1$s</string>
    <string name="buy_transfer">Buy or transfer</string>
    <string name="calculate_miner_fee">Calculate network fee</string>
    <string name="calculating_fees">Calculating Fee</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cant_contact_us_message">Visit help.coinbase.com/en/more/coinbase-wallet</string>
    <string name="cashaddr">CashAddr</string>
    <string name="catalyst_change_bundle_location">Change Bundle Location</string>
    <string name="catalyst_copy_button">"Copy
"</string>
    <string name="catalyst_debug">Debug</string>
    <string name="catalyst_debug_chrome">Debug with Chrome</string>
    <string name="catalyst_debug_chrome_stop">Stop Chrome Debugging</string>
    <string name="catalyst_debug_connecting">Connecting to debugger...</string>
    <string name="catalyst_debug_error">Failed to connect to debugger!</string>
    <string name="catalyst_debug_nuclide">Debug with Nuclide</string>
    <string name="catalyst_debug_nuclide_error">Failed to communicate with the bundler to enabling debugging with Nuclide.</string>
    <string name="catalyst_debug_stop">Stop Debugging</string>
    <string name="catalyst_dismiss_button">"Dismiss
(ESC)"</string>
    <string name="catalyst_heap_capture">Capture Heap</string>
    <string name="catalyst_hot_reloading">Enable Fast Refresh</string>
    <string name="catalyst_hot_reloading_auto_disable">Disabling Fast Refresh because it requires a development bundle.</string>
    <string name="catalyst_hot_reloading_auto_enable">Switching to development bundle in order to enable Fast Refresh.</string>
    <string name="catalyst_hot_reloading_stop">Disable Fast Refresh</string>
    <string name="catalyst_inspector">Toggle Inspector</string>
    <string name="catalyst_loading_from_url">Loading from %1$s…</string>
    <string name="catalyst_perf_monitor">Show Perf Monitor</string>
    <string name="catalyst_perf_monitor_stop">Hide Perf Monitor</string>
    <string name="catalyst_reload">Reload</string>
    <string name="catalyst_reload_button">"Reload
(R, R)"</string>
    <string name="catalyst_reload_error">Failed to load bundle. Try restarting the bundler or reconnecting your device.</string>
    <string name="catalyst_report_button">Report</string>
    <string name="catalyst_sample_profiler_disable">Disable Sampling Profiler</string>
    <string name="catalyst_sample_profiler_enable">Enable Sampling Profiler</string>
    <string name="catalyst_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="catalyst_settings_title">Debug Settings</string>
    <string name="change_network">Change network</string>
    <string name="change_pin">Change PIN</string>
    <string name="character_counter_content_description">Character limit exceeded %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern">%1$d / %2$d</string>
    <string name="choose_amount">Choose amount</string>
    <string name="choose_coin">Choose crypto</string>
    <string name="choose_provider">Choose provider</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="cloud_backup_backup_now">Backup now</string>
    <string name="cloud_backup_dialog_message">Take 2 minutes to back up your wallet, and never risk losing your money.</string>
    <string name="cloud_backup_dialog_title">"Don't risk your money"</string>
    <string name="cloud_backup_later">Later</string>
    <string name="cloud_backup_password_recovery_disclaimer">I understand that Coinbase cannot recover this password for me.</string>
    <string name="coinbase">Coinbase</string>
    <string name="coinbase_consumer_privacy_url">https://www.coinbase.com/legal/privacy</string>
    <string name="coinbase_consumer_tos_url">https://www.coinbase.com/legal/user_agreement</string>
    <string name="coinbase_fee">Coinbase Fee</string>
    <string name="coinbase_wallet_description">"The easiest and most secure
crypto wallet"</string>
    <string name="coins">Coins</string>
    <string name="collectible_items_error">Error while fetching NFTs</string>
    <string name="collectibles">NFTs</string>
    <string name="com.crashlytics.android.build_id">a7e262da43b94279894b65a5b27ca322</string>
    <string name="combine">%1$s %2$s</string>
    <string name="combobox_description">Combo Box</string>
    <string name="coming_soon_to_wallet">Coming soon to Wallet</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_button">Enable</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_text">"%1$s won't work unless you enable Google Play services."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_title">Enable Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_button">Install</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_text">"%1$s won't run without Google Play services, which are missing from your device."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_title">Get Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_channel_name">Google Play services availability</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_ticker">Google Play services error</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">%1$s is having trouble with Google Play services. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_text">"%1$s won't run without Google Play services, which are not supported by your device."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_button">Update</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_text">"%1$s won't run unless you update Google Play services."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_title">Update Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_updating_text">"%1$s won't run without Google Play services, which are currently updating."</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_wear_update_text">New version of Google Play services needed. It will update itself shortly.</string>
    <string name="common_open_on_phone">Open on phone</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text">Sign in</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text_long">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="complete_connection">Complete connection</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="confirm_button_add_card">Add debit card</string>
    <string name="confirm_button_buy">Buy</string>
    <string name="confirm_button_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="confirm_coinbase_balance">Coinbase balance</string>
    <string name="confirm_device_credential_password">Use password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="confirm_pin">Confirm your code</string>
    <string name="confirmation_amount">@string/amount</string>
    <string name="confirmation_buy_transfer_explanation">Buying from Coinbase and transferring to your Wallet</string>
    <string name="confirmation_coinbase_fees">Coinbase fee</string>
    <string name="confirmation_details">Details</string>
    <string name="confirmation_error_coin_selection">Transaction could not be created. You may not have enough balance to pay for the network fee. Please try again with a smaller amount.</string>
    <string name="confirmation_estimated_amount">Estimated amount</string>
    <string name="confirmation_estimated_network_fees">Network Fee</string>
    <string name="confirmation_processed_by_worldpay">Processed by Coinbase UK, Ltd., 107 Cheapside, London EC2V 6DN</string>
    <string name="confirmation_send_transfer_explanation">Transferring from your Coinbase balance to your Wallet</string>
    <string name="confirmation_total_fees">Total</string>
    <string name="connect_accounts">Connect accounts</string>
    <string name="connect_accounts_now">Connect to Coinbase</string>
    <string name="connect_to_coinbase">Connect to Coinbase</string>
    <string name="connections">CONNECTIONS</string>
    <string name="consumer_account">Consumer Account</string>
    <string name="consumer_account_label">Coinbase balance</string>
    <string name="consumer_add_payment_method">Add a new payment method</string>
    <string name="consumer_add_transfer_method">Add payment method</string>
    <string name="consumer_add_transfer_method_subtext">None of your funding methods will cover this transaction. Try adding a new card.</string>
    <string name="consumer_card_cdv">Verify your card</string>
    <string name="consumer_card_cdv_description">If there are more than two holds, please enter the two largest amounts. You will not be charged for these transactions.</string>
    <string name="consumer_card_cdv_explanation">Enter the 2 amounts deposited from your card</string>
    <string name="consumer_card_cdv_title">Verify the two pending holds of $1.01 or greater from Coinbase.</string>
    <string name="consumer_cdv_error">Error verifying deposit amounts</string>
    <string name="consumer_choose_transfer_method">Choose one for this transaction</string>
    <string name="consumer_confirm_buy">BUY FROM COINBASE</string>
    <string name="consumer_confirm_send">TRANSFER</string>
    <string name="consumer_connect_cta_description">Easily transfer coins from your Coinbase account to Wallet. Start by connecting your Coinbase account.</string>
    <string name="consumer_connect_cta_description_onramp">Easily buy or transfer coins from your Coinbase account to Wallet. Start by connecting your Coinbase account.</string>
    <string name="consumer_connect_cta_title">A new way to transfer from Coinbase</string>
    <string name="consumer_connect_cta_title_onramp">A new way to buy and transfer from Coinbase</string>
    <string name="consumer_connect_later">Later</string>
    <string name="consumer_connect_onramp_privacy_details">Coinbase is a separate service that lets you buy crypto. Connect or sign up for an account now.</string>
    <string name="consumer_connect_onramp_privacy_title">Buy or transfer from Coinbase</string>
    <string name="consumer_connect_privacy_notice_body">Transfer coins easily from your Coinbase.com account to your Wallet app. Please note that making this link also ties your Coinbase.com identity to this Wallet.</string>
    <string name="consumer_connect_privacy_notice_fine_print">"Use of Coinbase.com's account linkage feature is subject to Coinbase.com's &lt;a href=%1$s style=color: #8899AA>User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href=%2$s style=color: #8899AA>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>."</string>
    <string name="consumer_create_account">Create your account</string>
    <string name="consumer_login_button">Connect my Coinbase account</string>
    <string name="consumer_opening_coinbase">Opening Coinbase</string>
    <string name="consumer_payment_method_immediate">Immediate</string>
    <string name="consumer_payment_method_not_yet_supported">Not yet available for use on Wallet</string>
    <string name="consumer_payment_method_verify">Verify this payment method</string>
    <string name="consumer_payment_methods">Payment Methods</string>
    <string name="consumer_settings_title">Settings for your Coinbase account</string>
    <string name="consumer_sign_up_button">Sign up for Coinbase</string>
    <string name="consumer_transfer">Transfer %1$s</string>
    <string name="consumer_transfer_available_balance">%1$s • %2$s available</string>
    <string name="consumer_transfer_daily_limit">Daily limit reached</string>
    <string name="consumer_transfer_daily_limit_subtext">"You've hit your daily purchase limit for this payment method. Please try another payment method or trying again tomorrow."</string>
    <string name="consumer_transfer_method">Pay with %1$s</string>
    <string name="consumer_transfer_method_coinbase">Coinbase</string>
    <string name="consumer_transfer_method_selector">%1$s%2$s</string>
    <string name="consumer_transfer_method_selector_header">Funding method</string>
    <string name="consumer_wbl_info_transfer_limit">Transfer limit reached</string>
    <string name="consumer_wbl_info_transfer_limit_subtext">You can only transfer %1$s today. To transfer more, please wait for your bank transfers to Coinbase.com to complete</string>
    <string name="consumer_wbl_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="continue_">Continue</string>
    <string name="copied">Copied</string>
    <string name="copied_to_clipboard">Copied to Clipboard</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="copy_cashaddr_address">Copy CashAddr address</string>
    <string name="copy_legacy_address">Copy Legacy address</string>
    <string name="copy_or_share">Copy or share</string>
    <string name="copy_or_share_address">Copy or share address</string>
    <string name="copy_segwit_address">Copy SegWit address</string>
    <string name="copy_to_clipboard">Copy to clipboard</string>
    <string name="create_new_wallet">Create a new wallet</string>
    <string name="create_password_info_continue">I understand</string>
    <string name="create_pin">Create PIN</string>
    <string name="currencies">Currencies</string>
    <string name="currency_name_code_format">%1$s (%2$s)</string>
    <string name="current_lock_method">Current lock method</string>
    <string name="custom">Custom</string>
    <string name="dapp_front_page">https://wallet.coinbase.com/dapps/</string>
    <string name="dapp_permission_authorize_button">Authorize</string>
    <string name="dapp_permission_deny_button">Deny</string>
    <string name="dapp_permission_info">%s will not be able to move funds without your permissions</string>
    <string name="dapp_permission_read_wallet">See your wallet balance and activity</string>
    <string name="dapp_permission_requests">Send you requests for transactions</string>
    <string name="dapp_permission_title">Authorize %s</string>
    <string name="dapp_search_hint">Search or type URL</string>
    <string name="dapps_description">Decentralized exchanges, jobs, NFTs and more!</string>
    <string name="dapps_title">Explore the universe of Decentralized Apps</string>
    <string name="debug_menu_title">Debug menu</string>
    <string name="default_error_msg">Unknown error</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">803983633230-957t3u1s2oua9tl5nlpdjacrq7fgn1g2.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="define_roundedimageview" />
    <string name="delete_google_drive_backup">Delete Google Drive backup</string>
    <string name="desc__consumer_transfer_initiated">It can take a few minutes for the transfer to complete.</string>
    <string name="description__pick_wallet">Multiple wallets found</string>
    <string name="description__restore_wallet">Restore your wallet with the 12 word recovery phrase or with Google Drive</string>
    <string name="destination_tag">Destination Tag</string>
    <string name="destination_tag_hint">Destination Tag (optional)…</string>
    <string name="destination_tag_invalid">Destination tag entered is invalid</string>
    <string name="destination_tag_label">Destination tag</string>
    <string name="develop_message">These features are for advanced users and developers only and will likely be removed or changed significantly in future updates.</string>
    <string name="device_lock">App Lock</string>
    <string name="digital_assets_descriptions">Take control of your tokens and NFTs by storing them on your own device</string>
    <string name="digital_assets_title">"All your digital assets in
one place"</string>
    <string name="disclaimer__enter_password">Coinbase does not store any of your data, so we cannot recover your password for you.</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="disconnect_account">Disconnect account</string>
    <string name="disconnect_account_description">You can always connect the account again later</string>
    <string name="disconnect_account_title">Disconnect account?</string>
    <string name="disconnect_all">Disconnect all</string>
    <string name="disconnect_all_dapps_title">Are you sure you want to disconnect from all DApps? You can always connect it again later</string>
    <string name="disconnect_dapp_title">Are you sure you want to disconnect from %1$s? You can always connect it again later</string>
    <string name="disconnect_walletlink">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="dont_show_again">"Don't show again"</string>
    <string name="earn_more">Earn more</string>
    <string name="ellipsize">…</string>
    <string name="empty" />
    <string name="empty_state_collectibles_message">Explore new NFTs in the Dapps tab.</string>
    <string name="empty_state_collectibles_title">No NFTs Yet!</string>
    <string name="enter_password_hint_label">At least 8 characters, with at least 1 number</string>
    <string name="enter_password_subtitle">Created for this wallet</string>
    <string name="error__fetching_cloud_backup_status">Error fetching cloud backup status.</string>
    <string name="error__fetching_google_account">Error fetching Google account.</string>
    <string name="error__generating_share_link">Error generating share link</string>
    <string name="error__invalid_special_characters">Invalid. No special characters allowed.</string>
    <string name="error__mnemonic_cloud_backup">Error while backing up mnemonic to the cloud.</string>
    <string name="error_creating_new_pin">Error creating new PIN</string>
    <string name="error_fetching_gas_data">Error fetching gas estimation data</string>
    <string name="error_getting_buy_status">Timed out waiting for buy to complete. Please visit coinbase.com to check your account</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">Incorrect password</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password_generic">Invalid password</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password_length">At least 8 characters</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password_requirements_not_met">Include at least 1 letter and 1 number</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_passwords_do_not_match">Does not match above</string>
    <string name="error_lockout">Biometric authentication is locked. Please try again in 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="error_lockout_permanent">Biometric authentication is locked. Please retry after locking and unlocking your device.</string>
    <string name="error_lockout_title">Too many attempts</string>
    <string name="error_no_backups_found">No backups found on Google Drive</string>
    <string name="error_occurred_try_again">Error occurred try again</string>
    <string name="error_sending_purchase_completed">Your purchase is complete on coinbase.com but there was an error transferring to Coinbase Wallet. Please check your account and try transferring again.</string>
    <string name="error_wallet_recovery_generic">Error while recovering wallet</string>
    <string name="estimated_amount">Estimated amount</string>
    <string name="estimated_times_based_on_price">Estimated times based on each price</string>
    <string name="eth_mainnets">Eth Mainnets</string>
    <string name="eth_testnets">Eth Testnets</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_scrim_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationScrimBehavior</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="fast">Fast</string>
    <string name="fast_wait_time">15 seconds</string>
    <string name="fatal_authentication_dialog_message">A fatal error occurred when trying to authenticate. You will need to recover your account using your 12 word Recovery Phrase.</string>
    <string name="fatal_authentication_dialog_title">Fatal Authentication Error</string>
    <string name="fcm_fallback_notification_channel_label">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="fees_info_url">https://help.coinbase.com/en/coinbase/trading-and-funding/pricing-and-fees/fees.html</string>
    <string name="fetch_max_error">Failed to fetch max amount</string>
    <string name="fiat_short_name_eur">Euros</string>
    <string name="fiat_short_name_gbp">Pounds</string>
    <string name="fiat_short_name_usd">Dollars</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_dialog_touch_sensor">Touch the fingerprint sensor</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_error_hw_not_available">Fingerprint hardware not available.</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_error_hw_not_present">This device does not have a fingerprint sensor</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_error_lockout">Too many attempts. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_error_no_fingerprints">No fingerprints enrolled.</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_error_user_canceled">Fingerprint operation canceled by user.</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_not_recognized">Not recognized</string>
    <string name="firebase_database_url">https://coinbase-wallet-production.firebaseio.com</string>
    <string name="flash">Toggle flash</string>
    <string name="from_elsewhere">Elsewhere</string>
    <string name="from_my_coinbase_account">From my Coinbase account</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_dapp_permission_approve_subtext">You can always disconnect from apps in Settings</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_dapp_permission_bullet1">Connect to crypto apps with your permission and reveal your public address</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_dapp_permission_bullet2">Send you requests for transactions</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_dapp_permission_bullet3">Move funds without your permission</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_dapp_permission_subtitle1">Would like to</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_dapp_permission_subtitle2">Will not be able to</string>
    <string name="fullscreen_dapp_permission_title">Coinbase Wallet extension</string>
    <string name="fund_action_convert_crypto">Convert crypto</string>
    <string name="fund_action_transfer_from_coinbase">Transfer from Coinbase</string>
    <string name="fund_action_transfer_from_coinbase_onramp">Buy or Transfer from Coinbase</string>
    <string name="fund_action_transfer_from_elsewhere">Transfer from elsewhere</string>
    <string name="fund_item_description">From Coinbase or elsewhere</string>
    <string name="fund_item_title_onramp_only">Buy or transfer</string>
    <string name="fund_item_title_swap_and_onramp">Buy, transfer or convert</string>
    <string name="fund_item_title_swap_only">Transfer or convert</string>
    <string name="fund_sheet_dialog_title">Get more crypto</string>
    <string name="gas_limit">Gas limit</string>
    <string name="gas_limit_low">Gas limit lower than recommended %1$s</string>
    <string name="gas_price">Gas price</string>
    <string name="gas_set_too_high">Might waste gas</string>
    <string name="gas_set_too_high_explanation">An excess of gas price or limit may result in waste of fees</string>
    <string name="gas_set_too_low">Gas set very low</string>
    <string name="gas_set_too_low_explanation">Low gas price or limit may result in transaction being stuck</string>
    <string name="gcm_defaultSenderId">803983633230</string>
    <string name="generic_error_user_canceled">Authentication canceled by user.</string>
    <string name="get_coins_button">Get coins</string>
    <string name="get_crypto_button">Get crypto</string>
    <string name="glide_license">" License for everything not in third_party and not otherwise marked: Copyright 2014 Google, Inc. All rights reserved. Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met: 1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer. 2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution. THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY GOOGLE, INC. ``AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL GOOGLE, INC. OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. The views and conclusions contained in the software and documentation are those of the authors and should not be interpreted as representing official policies, either expressed or implied, of Google, Inc. --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- License for third_party/disklrucache: Copyright 2012 Jake Wharton Copyright 2011 The Android Open Source Project Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the License); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an AS IS BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License. --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- License for third_party/gif_decoder: Copyright (c) 2013 Xcellent Creations, Inc. Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the Software), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions: The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software. THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED AS IS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE. --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- License for third_party/gif_encoder/AnimatedGifEncoder.java and third_party/gif_encoder/LZWEncoder.java: No copyright asserted on the source code of this class. May be used for any purpose, however, refer to the Unisys LZW patent for restrictions on use of the associated LZWEncoder class. Please forward any corrections to kweiner@fmsware.com. ----------------------------------------------------------------------------- License for third_party/gif_encoder/NeuQuant.java Copyright (c) 1994 Anthony Dekker NEUQUANT Neural-Net quantization algorithm by Anthony Dekker, 1994. See Kohonen neural networks for optimal colour quantization in Network:
        Computation in Neural Systems Vol. 5 (1994) pp 351-367. for a discussion of the algorithm. Any party obtaining a copy of these files from the author, directly or indirectly, is granted, free of charge, a full and unrestricted irrevocable, world-wide, paid up, royalty-free, nonexclusive right and license to deal in this software and documentation files (the Software), including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons who receive copies from any such party to do so, with the only requirement being that this copyright notice remain intact. "</string>
    <string name="global_send_no_coins_found_subtitle">Send yourself some coins</string>
    <string name="global_send_no_coins_found_title">No coins found</string>
    <string name="google_api_key">AIzaSyBdl7pgS6_r7UNl3Bbb3p23bnrzNRKkh2c</string>
    <string name="google_app_id">1:803983633230:android:9c5d4aea033e4271</string>
    <string name="google_crash_reporting_api_key">AIzaSyBdl7pgS6_r7UNl3Bbb3p23bnrzNRKkh2c</string>
    <string name="google_play_services_is_unavailable">Google Play Services is unavailable - some features may not work as intended.</string>
    <string name="google_search_url">https://www.google.com/search?q=%1$s</string>
    <string name="google_storage_bucket">coinbase-wallet-production.appspot.com</string>
    <string name="got_it">Got it</string>
    <string name="gwei">Gwei</string>
    <string name="header_description">Heading</string>
    <string name="hide_bottom_view_on_scroll_behavior">com.google.android.material.behavior.HideBottomViewOnScrollBehavior</string>
    <string name="i_understand">I understand</string>
    <string name="image_description">Image</string>
    <string name="imagebutton_description">Button, Image</string>
    <string name="incorrect">Incorrect</string>
    <string name="info__create_password">"We require you to set a password for your Cloud backup. This is to ensure that only you can restore your wallet.

Do not lose this password, Coinbase will not be able to reset it for you."</string>
    <string name="info_did_you_know_bch_desc">"Wallet supports &lt;b>CashAddr&lt;/b> and &lt;b>Legacy&lt;/b> address formats. Try using &lt;b>CashAddr&lt;/b> first, and if that doesn't work, use &lt;b>Legacy&lt;/b>."</string>
    <string name="info_did_you_know_bch_title">CashAddr vs. Legacy</string>
    <string name="info_did_you_know_btc_desc">Wallet supports &lt;b>Legacy&lt;/b> and &lt;b>SegWit&lt;/b> addresses. &lt;b>SegWit&lt;/b> allows lower fees but is not yet supported everywhere. If you can’t use &lt;b>SegWit&lt;/b> for a transaction, try using the &lt;b>Legacy&lt;/b> address instead.</string>
    <string name="info_did_you_know_btc_title">SegWit vs. Legacy</string>
    <string name="info_did_you_know_erc20_desc">ERC20 tokens are issued on the Ethereum blockchain. That means you can use your ETH wallet address to receive any ERC20 token!</string>
    <string name="info_did_you_know_erc20_title">Did you know?</string>
    <string name="info_did_you_know_ltc_desc">Wallet supports &lt;b>Legacy&lt;/b> and &lt;b>SegWit&lt;/b> addresses. &lt;b>SegWit&lt;/b> allows lower fees but is not yet supported everywhere. If you can’t use &lt;b>SegWit&lt;/b> for a transaction, try using the &lt;b>Legacy&lt;/b> address instead.</string>
    <string name="info_did_you_know_ltc_title">SegWit vs. Legacy</string>
    <string name="info_minimum_balance_warning">Minimum balance warning</string>
    <string name="info_replay_warning_description">Since the BCH/BSV chain fork on Nov 15, 2018, transactions you make on the BCH blockchain can result in the transactions also being made on the BSV chain. This vulnerability is called a replay attack. We will display this warning until either of these chains provide replay protection.</string>
    <string name="info_replay_warning_message">Replay warning</string>
    <string name="insufficient_balance_error">"You don't have enough %1$s to cover the network fee. Deposit at least %2$s into your wallet and try again."</string>
    <string name="insufficient_balance_no_fee_error">"You don't have enough %1$s to cover the network fee."</string>
    <string name="insufficient_balance_with_fiat_error">"You don't have enough %1$s to cover the network fee. Deposit at least %2$s (%3$s) and try again."</string>
    <string name="insufficient_fee_balance_info_prompt_subtitle">You are trying to send an ERC20 token, which are issued on the Ethereum blockchain. This means you need ETH to pay the miner’s fee to send this coin.</string>
    <string name="invalid_pin_length">Invalid PIN length</string>
    <string name="invalid_qr_code">Invalid QR code</string>
    <string name="invalid_recovery_phrase">Invalid recovery phrase</string>
    <string name="invalid_verification_code">Invalid verification code</string>
    <string name="key_invalidated_dialog_info">Since you recently made changes to your device’s fingerprint data, you will need to recover your account using your 12 word Recovery Phrase. This is a security measure to protect your wallet.</string>
    <string name="key_invalidated_dialog_title">Key permanently invalidated</string>
    <string name="key_invalidated_notification">Looks like you’ve updated your device’s fingerprint or face authentication. You’ve been signed out and need to sign back in.</string>
    <string name="key_invalidated_notification_title">Biometrics Updated</string>
    <string name="l2_feature_disabled_token_transfer_text">ERC-20 transfers are currently disabled. Proceed with caution. Coinbase does not operate the Optimism network. Please do your own research before transacting.</string>
    <string name="l2_feature_disabled_token_transfer_title">Optimism is still in Beta</string>
    <string name="l2_optimism_in_beta_text">Proceed with caution. Coinbase does not operate the Optimism network. Please do your own research before transacting.</string>
    <string name="l2_optimism_in_beta_title">Optimism is still in Beta</string>
    <string name="l2_txhistory_unavailable_body">"We do not support full transaction history on %1$s. You'll only be able to see transactions in your wallet history that are created within Coinbase Wallet. That history will not be persisted within the app after logout."</string>
    <string name="l2_txhistory_unavailable_title">Full Transaction History Unavailable</string>
    <string name="label__2fa_enter_code">Enter code</string>
    <string name="label__2fa_verification">Either from SMS or authenticator app</string>
    <string name="label__coinbase_fees">Coinbase Fees</string>
    <string name="label__consumer_send_error">"Failed sending, check you're connected to the internet."</string>
    <string name="label__consumer_send_load_error">"Failed loading send info, check you're connected to the internet"</string>
    <string name="label__continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="label__create_password">Create password</string>
    <string name="label__create_password_subtitle">To encrypt the backup</string>
    <string name="label__enter_password">Enter password</string>
    <string name="label__estimate_miner_fee">Estimated network fee</string>
    <string name="label__password">Password</string>
    <string name="label__payment_method_fees">Payment Method Fees</string>
    <string name="label__restore_from_cloud">Restore from Google Drive</string>
    <string name="label__restore_manually">Restore with recovery phrase</string>
    <string name="label__transfer_from_coinbase">Transfer from Coinbase to Wallet</string>
    <string name="label__transfer_from_coinbase_onramp">Buy or transfer from Coinbase to Wallet</string>
    <string name="label__valid_passwords_match">Passwords match</string>
    <string name="later">Later</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn more.</string>
    <string name="legacy">Legacy</string>
    <string name="legal">Legal</string>
    <string name="lend_balance_toolbar">%1$s</string>
    <string name="lend_coin_apr">%1$s %%</string>
    <string name="lend_coin_apr_min_max">%1$s–%2$s %%</string>
    <string name="lend_confirm_button">Lend</string>
    <string name="lend_confirm_from">FROM</string>
    <string name="lend_confirm_title">LEND</string>
    <string name="lend_confirm_to">TO</string>
    <string name="lend_confirm_withdraw_button">Withdraw</string>
    <string name="lend_confirm_withdraw_title">WITHDRAW</string>
    <string name="lend_continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="lend_dashboard_action_title">%1$s at %2$s with %3$s</string>
    <string name="lend_dashboard_calculating">Calculating</string>
    <string name="lend_dashboard_earn">Earn more interest</string>
    <string name="lend_dashboard_earn_more_label">Interest earned to date</string>
    <string name="lend_dashboard_interest_apr">"Earning interest
at %1$s%% APR"</string>
    <string name="lend_dashboard_interest_apr_title">Earning interest at %1$s%% APR</string>
    <string name="lend_dashboard_item_percent_apr">%1$s%% APR</string>
    <string name="lend_dashboard_loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="lend_dashboard_not_earning_interest">Not earning interest</string>
    <string name="lend_item_description_has_balance">At %1$s%% APR</string>
    <string name="lend_item_description_no_balance">Up to %1$s%% APR</string>
    <string name="lend_item_loading">Loading interest rate</string>
    <string name="lend_item_title_has_balance">Earning interest</string>
    <string name="lend_item_title_no_balance">Earn interest on your crypto</string>
    <string name="lend_more">Lend more</string>
    <string name="lend_provider_disabled_message">This provider is temporarily unavailable</string>
    <string name="lend_provider_disabled_title">Provider disabled</string>
    <string name="lend_send_apr">Earn ~%1$s annual interest at %2$s%% APR</string>
    <string name="lend_send_apr_abbreviated">~%1$s at %2$s%% APR</string>
    <string name="lend_send_available_balance">You have %1$s</string>
    <string name="lend_send_choose_amount">Choose amount</string>
    <string name="lend_send_lending_balance">"You're lending %1$s"</string>
    <string name="lend_send_withdraw_amount">Withdraw amount</string>
    <string name="lend_test_requirement_message">In order to earn interest with your crypto, please select the Ethereum network from settings</string>
    <string name="lend_user_agreement_button_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="lend_user_agreement_button_start">Start</string>
    <string name="lend_user_agreement_checkbox_text">I understand the risks associated with lending</string>
    <string name="lend_user_agreement_page_1_body">Earn interest by lending out your crypto with smart contracts. These contracts are blockchain-based apps that accept your crypto and lend it out to borrowers who pay interest. Interest rates fluctuate dynamically based on supply and demand.</string>
    <string name="lend_user_agreement_page_1_title">Earn interest on your crypto</string>
    <string name="lend_user_agreement_page_2_body">"Lending happens via third party smart contracts, and not through Coinbase. Research the contract providers before you lend.

Returns aren’t guaranteed. While loans are backed by collateral, there are still risks. Crypto apps are new and evolving - they may have bugs that cause you to lose funds. Or, in the event of a large price drop, there may be insufficient collateral to return all your funds."</string>
    <string name="lend_user_agreement_page_2_title">Proceed with caution</string>
    <string name="library_roundedimageview_author">Vince Mi</string>
    <string name="library_roundedimageview_authorWebsite">https://github.com/vinc3m1</string>
    <string name="library_roundedimageview_isOpenSource">true</string>
    <string name="library_roundedimageview_libraryDescription">A fast ImageView (and Drawable) that supports rounded corners (and ovals or circles) based on the original example from Romain Guy.</string>
    <string name="library_roundedimageview_libraryName">RoundedImageView</string>
    <string name="library_roundedimageview_libraryVersion">1.3.0</string>
    <string name="library_roundedimageview_libraryWebsite">https://github.com/vinc3m1/RoundedImageView</string>
    <string name="library_roundedimageview_licenseId">apache_2_0</string>
    <string name="library_roundedimageview_repositoryLink">https://github.com/vinc3m1/RoundedImageView.git</string>
    <string name="link_description">Link</string>
    <string name="link_failed">Link failed</string>
    <string name="link_wallet_to_coinbase">Link your Wallet to Coinbase.com</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="local_currency">Local currency</string>
    <string name="lock_method">Lock method</string>
    <string name="login_email_hint">you@domain.com</string>
    <string name="login_email_prompt">EMAIL</string>
    <string name="login_first_name_hint">First Name</string>
    <string name="login_first_name_label">FIRST NAME</string>
    <string name="login_last_name_hint">Last Name</string>
    <string name="login_last_name_label">LAST NAME</string>
    <string name="login_password_prompt">PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="manual_backup">Manual backup</string>
    <string name="manual_backup_copy_to_clipboard_clear">Copied for 1 minute</string>
    <string name="manual_setting">Manual setting</string>
    <string name="max">Max</string>
    <string name="max_fee">Max fee</string>
    <string name="max_fee_low">Max fee lower than recommended %1$s gwei</string>
    <string name="max_fee_per_gas">Max fee per gas = %1$s</string>
    <string name="mcd_dai_description">The Maker project deprecated Single-Collateral Dai (SAI) tokens on May 12. Your SAI tokens are redeemable for Ethereum through the official Maker tool.</string>
    <string name="mcd_dai_maker_dapp">Open conversion tool</string>
    <string name="mcd_dai_title">SAI is shutting down</string>
    <string name="memo_hash">Memo Hash</string>
    <string name="memo_id">Memo ID</string>
    <string name="memo_return">Memo Return</string>
    <string name="memo_text">Memo Text</string>
    <string name="menu_description">Menu</string>
    <string name="menubar_description">Menu Bar</string>
    <string name="menuitem_description">Menu Item</string>
    <string name="message_approve_button">Approve</string>
    <string name="message_cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="message_sign_button">Sign</string>
    <string name="message_signer_description">Signatures can be used to prove you own this wallet account, to allow asset transfers, or for other purposes. Only sign messages from DApps you trust.</string>
    <string name="message_signer_details_title">MESSAGE FROM DAPP</string>
    <string name="message_signer_error">No human readable message was provided. Make sure you trust the DApp before signing.</string>
    <string name="message_signer_title">Signature request</string>
    <string name="message_switch_body">Switch to %1$s network</string>
    <string name="message_switch_title">Switch Ethereum chain</string>
    <string name="metadata_tag_and_value">%1$s %2$s</string>
    <string name="min_option_requirement_notice">At least one option must be selected.</string>
    <string name="miner_fee">Network fee</string>
    <string name="miner_fee_1559_postfix">We provide an estimated fee range for the amount required to complete the transaction.</string>
    <string name="minimum_balance_send_warning">Max send amount: %1$s</string>
    <string name="minimum_reserve_send_balance_explanation">The %1$s ledger requires that all wallets have a minimum balance of %2$s. You cannot send an amount that would bring your balance below %2$s.</string>
    <string name="minimum_reserve_send_balance_title">Minimum %1$s balance</string>
    <string name="mit_license">" Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the Software), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions: The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software. THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED AS IS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE. "</string>
    <string name="mm_isc_license">" ISC License Copyright (c) 2020 MetaMask Permission to use, copy, modify, and/or distribute this software for any purpose with or without fee is hereby granted, provided that the above copyright notice and this permission notice appear in all copies. THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED AS IS AND THE AUTHOR DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO THIS SOFTWARE INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS SOFTWARE. "</string>
    <string name="mm_mit_license">" MIT License Copyright (c) 2018 MetaMask Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the Software), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions: The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software. THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED AS IS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE "</string>
    <string name="mnemonic_backed_up">Backed up</string>
    <string name="mnemonic_backed_up_manually">Backed up manually</string>
    <string name="mnemonic_backup_account_info">Backed up under <b>%s</b></string>
    <string name="mnemonic_backup_info">These 12 words are the keys to your wallet. Back it up on the cloud or back it up manually. Do not share this with anyone.</string>
    <string name="mnemonic_not_backed_up">Not backed up</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="mtrl_chip_close_icon_content_description">Remove %1$s</string>
    <string name="nakamoto_entity_format" formatted="false">%s and %d</string>
    <string name="nav_app_bar_navigate_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="nav_app_bar_open_drawer_description">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="network_changed">Network changed</string>
    <string name="network_develop_message">Changing the network allows you to test developed apps without the risk of losing money. It’s recommended not to change these settings unless you are a developer.</string>
    <string name="network_unavailable">Network unavailable. Check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="next_action_error">Failed to process request. Check your network and try again.</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="no_biometric_dialog_message">"You recently deleted all of your device's fingerprint data. Please add a fingerprint to your Security settings and try again."</string>
    <string name="no_biometric_title">No Biometrics Found</string>
    <string name="no_results">No Results</string>
    <string name="no_thanks">No thanks</string>
    <string name="no_transactions_subtext">Your transactions will show up here</string>
    <string name="no_transactions_title">No transactions</string>
    <string name="nonce">Nonce</string>
    <string name="normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="normal_wait_time">30 seconds</string>
    <string name="not_available">Not available</string>
    <string name="not_really">Not really</string>
    <string name="not_yet_supported">Not yet supported by Wallet</string>
    <string name="notification_body_dapp_permission">%s is requesting access to your Ethereum account</string>
    <string name="notification_body_sign_and_submit_tx">%s is requesting a transaction</string>
    <string name="notification_body_sign_message">%s is requesting your signature</string>
    <string name="notification_body_submit_tx">%s would like to submit a transaction</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_name">WalletLink</string>
    <string name="notification_title_dapp_permission">Ethereum wallet access</string>
    <string name="notification_title_sign_and_submit_tx">Sign and submit transaction</string>
    <string name="notification_title_sign_message">Sign message</string>
    <string name="notification_title_submit_tx">Submit transaction</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="onboarding_pick_username_subtitle">This is how other Wallet users can find you and send you payments.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_pick_username_title">Pick your username</string>
    <string name="open_source_licenses">Acknowledgements</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="parent_dapp_permission_allow_button">Allow</string>
    <string name="parent_dapp_permission_cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="password_hint">8 characters or more</string>
    <string name="password_toggle_content_description">Show password</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye">M12,4.5C7,4.5 2.73,7.61 1,12c1.73,4.39 6,7.5 11,7.5s9.27,-3.11 11,-7.5c-1.73,-4.39 -6,-7.5 -11,-7.5zM12,17c-2.76,0 -5,-2.24 -5,-5s2.24,-5 5,-5 5,2.24 5,5 -2.24,5 -5,5zM12,9c-1.66,0 -3,1.34 -3,3s1.34,3 3,3 3,-1.34 3,-3 -1.34,-3 -3,-3z</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye_mask_strike_through">M2,4.27 L19.73,22 L22.27,19.46 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1 L23,1 L23,23 L1,23 L1,4.27 Z</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye_mask_visible">M2,4.27 L2,4.27 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1 L23,1 L23,23 L1,23 L1,4.27 Z</string>
    <string name="path_password_strike_through">M3.27,4.27 L19.74,20.74</string>
    <string name="pay_with">Pay with %1$s</string>
    <string name="payment_address">Payment address</string>
    <string name="pin">PIN</string>
    <string name="pin_error">PIN does not match. Please re-enter the same PIN or start again.</string>
    <string name="pin_success">Confirmed!</string>
    <string name="placeholder_notification_count">1 of 1</string>
    <string name="please_authenticate">Please Authenticate</string>
    <string name="prefixed_username">\@%s</string>
    <string name="priority_fee">Priority fee</string>
    <string name="priority_fee_low">Priority fee lower than recommended %1$s gwei</string>
    <string name="privacy_explanation">Crypto transactions take place on public blockchains. When your username is set to Public, advanced users can look up your addresses on the blockchain and view your transaction history.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_url">https://wallet.coinbase.com/privacy-policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_private">Private</string>
    <string name="privacy_private_explanation">Other Wallet users cannot search for my username</string>
    <string name="privacy_public">Public</string>
    <string name="privacy_public_explanation">Other Wallet users can search for my username and send me crypto</string>
    <string name="privacy_recommended">Recommended</string>
    <string name="privacy_settings_header">Privacy Settings</string>
    <string name="privacy_settings_onboarding_description">You can always change this later in Settings</string>
    <string name="privacy_settings_onboarding_header">Set your privacy preferences</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="profile__unknown_username">Wallet User</string>
    <string name="progressbar_description">Progress Bar</string>
    <string name="project_id">coinbase-wallet-production</string>
    <string name="prompt_coinbase_fee_body">"In addition to the displayed Coinbase fee, we include a spread in the exchange rate. Cryptocurrency markets are volatile, and this allows us to temporarily lock in a price for trade execution.
&lt;a href=https://help.coinbase.com/en/coinbase/trading-and-funding/pricing-and-fees/fees.html style=color: #8899AA>Learn more&lt;/a>"</string>
    <string name="prompt_coinbase_fee_title">Coinbase fee</string>
    <string name="prompt_high_fees_message">Just a heads up: network fees are high right now due to blockchain congestion. The network fee goes to the miner, not Coinbase, and applies to all transactions on the blockchain.</string>
    <string name="prompt_high_fees_title">Network fees are high right now</string>
    <string name="prompt_high_price_impact_message">You may not be getting the best price on this trade, either because your trade size is very large, or because you are trading a coin with low liquidity on DEXes. A smaller trade size may result in a better exchange rate.</string>
    <string name="prompt_high_price_impact_title">High price impact</string>
    <string name="prompt_learn_more">Learn more</string>
    <string name="protect_your_wallet">Protect your wallet</string>
    <string name="provider_info_assets_description">Amount of money this provider manages</string>
    <string name="provider_info_assets_title">Assets under custody</string>
    <string name="provider_info_collateral_description">The amount borrowers must lock up to secure their loan</string>
    <string name="provider_info_collateral_title">Minimum Collateral</string>
    <string name="provider_info_utilization_description">How much of it is loaned out</string>
    <string name="provider_info_utilization_title">Utilization</string>
    <string name="provider_prompt_auc_message">This is the value of crypto currently deposited to this smart contract. Contracts with lower AUC are more likely to experience high utilization, and therefore delayed withdrawals.</string>
    <string name="provider_prompt_auc_title">Assets under custody</string>
    <string name="provider_prompt_collateral_message">This is the minimum collateral that borrowers must deposit in order to borrow. For example, if collateral is 1.5x, a borrower must deposit at least 1.5 ETH in order to borrow 1 ETH. The higher the collateral, the greater the cushion against drops in crypto prices.</string>
    <string name="provider_prompt_collateral_title">Collateral</string>
    <string name="provider_prompt_not_applicable">n/a</string>
    <string name="provider_prompt_utilization_message">This is the percentage of crypto that has already been loaned out. In the event that many lenders are trying to withdraw at the same time, contracts with high utilization may have insufficient crypto to fulfill all withdrawal requests.</string>
    <string name="provider_prompt_utilization_title">Utilization</string>
    <string name="radiogroup_description">Radio Group</string>
    <string name="random_eth_address">0xc782696891dc3ffade1aa3c43cd51d14e0a95154</string>
    <string name="rate_on_playstore">Rate on Play Store</string>
    <string name="read_more_recovery_phrase_subtitle">"To sign into Coinbase Wallet you need to enter the 12-word recovery phrase that was given to you when you secured your account. You may import a wallet from Metamask, TrustWallet, or other wallets by using the recovery phrase provided in those apps.

Your account is stored anonymously on the Ethereum blockchain. This means we don’t have access to your data. The 12-word recovery phrase is the only way to sign in to your account. There is no way to recover your account if you have lost the phrase.

You cannot sign into Wallet with your Coinbase.com account."</string>
    <string name="read_more_recovery_phrase_title">What is a recovery phrase?</string>
    <string name="ready_to_transfer_coins">Ready to transfer coins</string>
    <string name="ready_to_transfer_coins_explanation">Congratulations! You can now easily transfer coins from Coinbase to your Wallet.</string>
    <string name="ready_to_transfer_coins_explanation_onramp">Congratulations! You can now easily buy or transfer crypto from Coinbase to your Wallet.</string>
    <string name="ready_to_transfer_coins_onramp">All done</string>
    <string name="receive">Receive</string>
    <string name="recipient">Recipient</string>
    <string name="recipient_disabled_incoming_transactions">The address you are sending to has disabled incoming transactions.</string>
    <string name="recipient_requires_base_reserve">The address you are sending to is not yet active.</string>
    <string name="recipient_requires_destination_tag">The address you are sending to requires a destination tag. Please enter one and try again.</string>
    <string name="recommended">Recommended</string>
    <string name="recovery_phrase">Recovery phrase</string>
    <string name="recovery_phrase_error_dialog_message">A fatal error occurred when trying to view your Recovery Phrase. You will need to recover your account using your 12 word Recovery Phrase.</string>
    <string name="recovery_phrase_error_dialog_title">Recovery Phrase Error</string>
    <string name="reload">Reload</string>
    <string name="remind_later">Remind me later</string>
    <string name="remove_bookmark">Remove Bookmark</string>
    <string name="removed_from_bookmarks">%s removed from Bookmarks.</string>
    <string name="require_for_transactions_desc">Require for transactions</string>
    <string name="require_to_open_app_desc">Require to open app</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="return_key">Return</string>
    <string name="review_legal_disclaimer">Please review the Coinbase Wallet Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="rn_tab_description">Tab</string>
    <string name="scan_qr">Scan QR</string>
    <string name="scan_qr_code">Scan QR code</string>
    <string name="scanning">Scanning</string>
    <string name="screenshot_warning_message">If you take a screenshot, your backup may be viewed by other apps</string>
    <string name="screenshot_warning_title">Screenshots are not secure</string>
    <string name="screenshots_are_not_secure_description">, please write these 12 words down, or copy it to a password manager.</string>
    <string name="scrollbar_description">Scroll Bar</string>
    <string name="search_description">Search Field</string>
    <string name="search_for_a_coin">Search for a coin…</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">Search</string>
    <string name="search_with_google">- Search with Google</string>
    <string name="security">Security</string>
    <string name="security_prompt_update_provider_cta_affirmative">Update</string>
    <string name="security_prompt_update_provider_message">You have an out-of-date Android Security Provider. We strongly encourage you to update your Android Security Provider to ensure safe app usage.</string>
    <string name="security_prompt_update_provider_title">Update Security Provider</string>
    <string name="security_prompt_verify_apps_cta_affirmative">Enable</string>
    <string name="security_prompt_verify_apps_message">To ensure safe usage of your wallet, we strongly encourage that you enable Play Protect to verify apps on your device.</string>
    <string name="security_prompt_verify_apps_title">Enable Verify Apps</string>
    <string name="segwit">SegWit</string>
    <string name="select_a_coin">Select a coin</string>
    <string name="select_transfer_method">Select</string>
    <string name="select_words_in_correct_order">Select words in correct order</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="send_complete_message">You sent %1$s to %2$s</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_button">Send</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_calculation_error">There was an error calculating the transaction fee, please try again to continue with your transaction.</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_details">Details</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_fee_eth_explainer">Why network fee is in %1$s</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_fee_explainer">What are network fees</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_from">FROM</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_miner_fee">NETWORK FEE</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_paying_with">PAYING WITH</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_title">SEND</string>
    <string name="send_confirm_to">TO</string>
    <string name="send_confirmation_miner_dialog_button">Got it</string>
    <string name="send_confirmation_miner_fee_dialog_title">About network fees</string>
    <string name="send_confirmation_no_amount">This dapp is requesting an action, which could take money from your wallet. Make sure you trust this site.</string>
    <string name="send_confirmation_pay_button">Pay</string>
    <string name="send_confirmation_title">Confirm Payment</string>
    <string name="send_confirmation_total">TOTAL</string>
    <string name="send_destination_address_error">Not a valid %s address</string>
    <string name="send_destination_empty_description">Sent addresses will be shown here</string>
    <string name="send_destination_empty_title">No recents</string>
    <string name="send_destination_metadata">Metadata</string>
    <string name="send_destination_metadata_number_format">Memo id must be a number</string>
    <string name="send_destination_metadata_xrp_placeholder">XRP destination tag</string>
    <string name="send_destination_norecent_details">Sent addresses will be shown here</string>
    <string name="send_destination_norecent_title">No recents</string>
    <string name="send_destination_noresult_details">"This recipient either doesn't exist or is set to private"</string>
    <string name="send_destination_noresult_title">No results</string>
    <string name="send_destination_qr_warning">Invalid %s QR code</string>
    <string name="send_destination_search_bar_placeholder">Search recipient</string>
    <string name="send_destination_stellar_metadata_hex_format">Memo must be a valid hex value</string>
    <string name="send_destination_stellar_metadata_hex_length">Memo must be exactly 64 letters in length</string>
    <string name="send_destination_stellar_metadata_too_long">Memo text must be 28 characters or less</string>
    <string name="send_destination_suggested">SUGGESTED</string>
    <string name="send_destination_tag_number_format">Destination tag must be a number</string>
    <string name="send_fee_error">Unable to determine fee, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="send_history_message">Your send history is now available for this coin. We are working hard to add history for inbound payments.</string>
    <string name="send_history_only">Send History Only</string>
    <string name="send_history_title">Send history</string>
    <string name="send_insufficient_balance">Insufficient Balance</string>
    <string name="send_miner_fee_description">The network fee applies to all transactions on the %s network, and is not paid to Coinbase.</string>
    <string name="send_miner_fee_erc20_description">The network fee goes to the miner, not Coinbase. The fee applies to all transactions sent on the blockchain, including tokens like %s.</string>
    <string name="send_receive_description">Pay anyone in the world with just their Coinbase Wallet username</string>
    <string name="send_receive_title">Easily send and receive cryptocurrency</string>
    <string name="send_to">Send to</string>
    <string name="send_to_paste_title">Paste from clipboard</string>
    <string name="send_to_username_feature_prompt_body">"You can now send and receive crypto with just your username @%1$s. Change your privacy preferences in Settings anytime. We've also launched support for ENS and sending back to your Coinbase account."</string>
    <string name="send_to_username_feature_prompt_title">Crypto just got easier</string>
    <string name="send_to_username_feature_prompt_view_settings_button_label">View settings</string>
    <string name="send_to_username_invalid_characters">Invalid characters</string>
    <string name="send_to_username_invalid_metadata">Not a valid %1$s</string>
    <string name="send_to_username_share_copy">Send me crypto @%1$s on my Coinbase Wallet. Get your own crypto wallet at wallet.coinbase.com</string>
    <string name="set_up_authentication_info">Add an extra layer of security to keep your crypto safe.</string>
    <string name="set_up_device_lock_info">You do not have any biometric authentication methods set up.</string>
    <string name="set_up_device_lock_title">Biometric Authentication</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="share_your_address">Share your address</string>
    <string name="shared_element_transition_wallet_card">wallet_card_shared_element_transition</string>
    <string name="show_my_qr_code">Show my QR code</string>
    <string name="sign_in_hint">Recovery phrase…</string>
    <string name="sign_in_length_error_message">Please insert 12 words</string>
    <string name="sign_in_subtitle">This is a 12 word phrase you were given when you created your previous wallet.</string>
    <string name="sign_in_title">Sign in with a recovery phrase</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="sign_out_confirmation_title">Are you sure you want to sign out?</string>
    <string name="sign_out_warning_message">Without this you will not be able to sign back in to your account.</string>
    <string name="sign_out_warning_title">Have you recorded your recovery phrase?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="sign_up_certify_agree_acknowledge">" I certify that I am 18 years of age or older, I agree to the &lt;a href=https://www.coinbase.com/legal/user_agreement>User Agreement&lt;/a>, and acknowledge the &lt;a href=https://www.coinbase.com/legal/privacy>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>."</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign up</string>
    <string name="signup_password_hint">Create a new password</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="slow">Slow</string>
    <string name="slow_wait_time">45+ seconds</string>
    <string name="spinbutton_description">Spin Button</string>
    <string name="start_transfer">Start transfer</string>
    <string name="start_transfer_onramp">Buy or transfer</string>
    <string name="state_busy_description">busy</string>
    <string name="state_collapsed_description">collapsed</string>
    <string name="state_expanded_description">expanded</string>
    <string name="state_mixed_description">mixed</string>
    <string name="state_off_description">off</string>
    <string name="state_on_description">on</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="stellar_minimum_balance">XLM Minimum Balance</string>
    <string name="stellar_minimum_balance_explanation">Stellar (XLM) requires that all wallets have a minimum balance of %1$s XLM. Please fund your account with at least %1$s XLM. This %1$s XLM will remain locked in your wallet, as Stellar does not allow you to spend it.</string>
    <string name="stellar_recipient_requires_minimum_balance">The address you are sending to is not yet active. You can activate it by sending at least $1 XLM to this address.</string>
    <string name="stop_loading">Stop loading</string>
    <string name="suggested">Suggested</string>
    <string name="summary_description">Summary</string>
    <string name="swap">Convert</string>
    <string name="swap_amount_picker_biometrics">Proceed to biometrics</string>
    <string name="swap_amount_picker_error_high_price_impact">HIGH PRICE IMPACT</string>
    <string name="swap_amount_picker_error_low_liquidity">NOT ENOUGH LIQUIDITY TO CONVERT</string>
    <string name="swap_amount_picker_next_subtitle">"We won't submit your transaction yet"</string>
    <string name="swap_amount_picker_pin">Proceed to pin</string>
    <string name="swap_amount_picker_server_error_ticker_1">SOMETHING WENT WRONG</string>
    <string name="swap_amount_picker_server_error_ticker_2">TRY AGAIN LATER</string>
    <string name="swap_asset_picker_empty_source">"You don't have this crypto in your wallet"</string>
    <string name="swap_asset_picker_empty_target">"This crypto isn't supported by Wallet yet"</string>
    <string name="swap_asset_picker_empty_title_source">Not found</string>
    <string name="swap_asset_picker_empty_title_target">Not yet supported</string>
    <string name="swap_asset_picker_search_hint">Search crypto</string>
    <string name="swap_asset_picker_title_source">Convert from</string>
    <string name="swap_asset_picker_title_target">Convert to</string>
    <string name="swap_button_title">Trade</string>
    <string name="swap_complete_message">Conversion started</string>
    <string name="swap_confirmation_error_high_price_impact">HIGH PRICE IMPACT</string>
    <string name="swap_confirmation_fee_calculation_failed">Unable to determine fee, please try again later</string>
    <string name="swap_confirmation_high_price_impact">Price is significantly worse than market rate.</string>
    <string name="swap_confirmation_high_price_impact_convert_anyway">Convert anyway</string>
    <string name="swap_confirmation_title">Convert on %1$s</string>
    <string name="swap_currency_mode">Swap Currency Mode</string>
    <string name="swap_disclosure_body">"This feature provides a software interface to convert your crypto on decentralized exchanges (DEXes). 

DEXes are protocols running on the Ethereum blockchain that enable easy conversion of tokens. When you use this software, you send your funds directly from your self custody Wallet to a DEX service like Uniswap or 0x API without using a centralized exchange."</string>
    <string name="swap_disclosure_title">Convert your crypto with DEXes</string>
    <string name="swap_insufficient_balance">INSUFFICIENT BALANCE</string>
    <string name="swap_main_card_convert">Convert</string>
    <string name="swap_main_choose_coin">Choose coin</string>
    <string name="swap_main_convert_all">Convert all</string>
    <string name="swap_main_equivalent_to_placeholder">Equivalent to ...</string>
    <string name="swap_main_fiat_card_to">To</string>
    <string name="swap_main_tab_crypto">Crypto</string>
    <string name="swap_main_tab_fiat">Dollars</string>
    <string name="swap_main_to">To</string>
    <string name="swap_non_convertible_token_prompt_body">"Wallet's token conversion feature relies on Decentralized Exchanges built on the Ethereum blockchain. As a result, only Ethereum-based tokens can be converted using this feature."</string>
    <string name="swap_non_convertible_token_prompt_title">Crypto not convertible</string>
    <string name="swap_not_convertible_header">NOT CONVERTIBLE</string>
    <string name="swap_prompt_coinbase_fee_body">Coinbase charges a service fee on token conversions. This fee covers the expense of providing and maintaining the Wallet software.</string>
    <string name="swap_prompt_coinbase_fee_body_fee">Coinbase charges a service fee of %1$s%% on token conversions. This fee covers the expense of providing and maintaining the Coinbase Wallet app.</string>
    <string name="swap_prompt_coinbase_fee_title">Coinbase fee</string>
    <string name="swap_prompt_estimated_amount_body">We convert crypto using a 3rd party decentralized exchange. Your trade will execute at a price within 2% of this estimate or the transaction will be canceled and your funds returned to your wallet.</string>
    <string name="swap_prompt_estimated_amount_title">Estimated amount</string>
    <string name="swap_tos_maybe_later">Maybe later</string>
    <string name="swap_tos_prompt_description">"You can now convert over 500 Ethereum tokens like USDC, DAI, WBTC and more through DEXs right from your Wallet! Try it out now. 

We've also updated our Terms of Service effective Dec 7, 2020."</string>
    <string name="swap_tos_prompt_title">Convert crypto more easily</string>
    <string name="swap_tos_try_converting">Try converting now</string>
    <string name="swap_unsupported_token_prompt_body">Wallet does not support the conversion of this crypto yet, but you can convert it on another decentralized exchange</string>
    <string name="swap_unsupported_token_prompt_title">Crypto not yet supported</string>
    <string name="swap_unsupported_token_prompt_warning">This will open a third party service with no affiliation to Coinbase. Use at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="tab_dapps">DApps</string>
    <string name="tab_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="tab_wallet">Wallet</string>
    <string name="tablist_description">Tab List</string>
    <string name="template_error_payment_address" formatted="false">You can only send %s to a valid %s address.</string>
    <string name="template_feedback_default_body">"
Thanks!

app-version: v%1$s
android-version: %2$s
sdk-version: %3$d
device: %4$s
model: %5$s
manufacturer: %6$s 


"</string>
    <string name="template_feedback_default_email_subject">Wallet Feedback [Android, v%1$s]</string>
    <string name="template_notification_count" formatted="false">%d of %d</string>
    <string name="template_receive_coin">Receive %1$s</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_url">https://wallet.coinbase.com/terms-of-service</string>
    <string name="time_unit_minute">~%1$s min</string>
    <string name="time_unit_second">~%1$s sec</string>
    <string name="timer_description">Timer</string>
    <string name="title__pick_wallet">Choose wallet</string>
    <string name="title__restore_wallet">Restore wallet</string>
    <string name="title__verification_code">Two-factor code</string>
    <string name="toolbar_description">Tool Bar</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="transaction_cell_fiat_amount" formatted="false">%s %s</string>
    <string name="transaction_completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="transaction_destination_created_contract">Created contract</string>
    <string name="transaction_failed">Failed</string>
    <string name="transaction_header_complete">Confirmed</string>
    <string name="transaction_header_failed">Failed</string>
    <string name="transaction_header_pending">Pending</string>
    <string name="transaction_initiated">Initiated</string>
    <string name="transaction_toolbar_payment_to">Payment to</string>
    <string name="transaction_toolbar_pending">Pending payment to</string>
    <string name="transactions_warning">Transactions may take a few minutes to complete</string>
    <string name="transfer">Transfer</string>
    <string name="transfer_buy_coins_from_coinbase">Buy or transfer crypto from your Coinbase account to Coinbase Wallet.</string>
    <string name="transfer_buy_coins_from_coinbase_with_last_transaction">Buy or transfer crypto from your Coinbase account to Coinbase Wallet. %1$s</string>
    <string name="transfer_coins_from_coinbase">Transfer coins from your Coinbase account into your Wallet.</string>
    <string name="transfer_coins_from_coinbase_last_transfer">Last transfer %1$s</string>
    <string name="transfer_coins_from_coinbase_with_last_transaction">Transfer coins from your Coinbase account into your Wallet. %1$s</string>
    <string name="transfer_initiated">Transfer initiated</string>
    <string name="transfer_later">Transfer later</string>
    <string name="transfer_later_onramp">Later</string>
    <string name="transfer_to_wallet">Transfer to Wallet</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try again</string>
    <string name="tx_title_completed_received">Payment from</string>
    <string name="tx_title_completed_sent">Payment to</string>
    <string name="tx_title_consumer_completed_received">Transfer from</string>
    <string name="tx_title_consumer_failed_received">Failed transfer from</string>
    <string name="tx_title_consumer_pending_received">Pending transfer from</string>
    <string name="tx_title_failed_received">Failed payment from</string>
    <string name="tx_title_failed_sent">Failed payment to</string>
    <string name="tx_title_pending_received">Pending payment from</string>
    <string name="tx_title_pending_sent">Pending payment to</string>
    <string name="tx_view_on_button_format">View on %1$s</string>
    <string name="type_your_pin">Type your PIN</string>
    <string name="unable_to_import_existing_wallet">Unable to import existing wallet</string>
    <string name="unable_to_import_existing_wallet_check_network_connection">Unable to import existing wallet, please check your network connection.</string>
    <string name="unable_to_restore_wallet">Unable to restore wallet</string>
    <string name="universal_qr_coin_not_found">Coin not found in your wallet</string>
    <string name="universal_qr_scanner_subtitle">"Send money or connect
to a desktop website"</string>
    <string name="universal_qr_warning">Invalid QR code</string>
    <string name="unverified">- unverified</string>
    <string name="unverified_payment_method"><u>Verify</u></string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="update_wallet_subtitle">Please update to the latest version of Coinbase Wallet to continue.</string>
    <string name="update_wallet_title">New Version Available</string>
    <string name="use_fingerprint">Use Fingerprint</string>
    <string name="use_max">Use Max</string>
    <string name="use_slider">Use slider</string>
    <string name="user_name_explanation">Accept payments from other Coinbase Wallet users</string>
    <string name="user_profile_setting">Profile</string>
    <string name="value_with_space_at_end">"%s "</string>
    <string name="verification_amounts_hint">00</string>
    <string name="verify_card">Verify card</string>
    <string name="verify_recovery_phrase_error">Wrong recovery phrase</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="wallet">Wallet</string>
    <string name="wallet_detail_convert_token_action">Convert %1$s</string>
    <string name="wallet_empty_scanning_subtitle">Scanning for all your coins, they will appear here as they load</string>
    <string name="wallet_empty_scanning_title">Looking for coins</string>
    <string name="wallet_link">WalletLink</string>
    <string name="wallet_link_browsers">%1$s Total</string>
    <string name="wallet_link_channel_id">wallet_link_channel_id</string>
    <string name="wallet_link_failed_message">There was a problem connecting your wallet to the website</string>
    <string name="wallet_no_coins_found_subtitle">Transfer coins from your Coinbase account or elsewhere</string>
    <string name="wallet_no_coins_found_subtitle_onramp">Buy or Transfer coins from your Coinbase account or elsewhere</string>
    <string name="wallet_no_coins_found_title">No coins found</string>
    <string name="wallet_no_username_default">Your Wallet</string>
    <string name="wallet_support_email">wallet.support@coinbase.com</string>
    <string name="walletlink_dapp_connection_completed">Your wallet is connected to %1$s</string>
    <string name="walletlink_dapp_name">DApp</string>
    <string name="walletlink_v1_dapp_title">Legacy WalletLink</string>
    <string name="wallets_section_actions">ACTIONS</string>
    <string name="wallets_section_balance">BALANCE</string>
    <string name="web_debugging_disabled">Web debugging disabled</string>
    <string name="web_debugging_enabled">Web debugging enabled</string>
    <string name="will_likely_fail">• Will likely fail</string>
    <string name="withdraw">Withdraw</string>
    <string name="write_down_recovery_phrase">Write down recovery phrase</string>
    <string name="write_these_words_down">Write these 12 words down, or copy them to a password manager.</string>
    <string name="xlm_memo_hash_label">Memo hash</string>
    <string name="xlm_memo_id_label">Memo ID</string>
    <string name="xlm_memo_return_label">Memo return</string>
    <string name="xlm_memo_text_label">Memo text</string>
    <string name="xrp_minimum_balance">XRP Minimum Balance</string>
    <string name="xrp_minimum_balance_explanation">The XRP ledger requires that all wallets have a minimum balance of %1$s XRP. Please fund your account with at least %1$s XRP. This %1$s XRP will remain locked in your wallet, as the XRP ledger does not allow you to spend it.</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="you_dont_have_this_crypto">"You don't have this crypto"</string>
    <string name="zero">0</string>
    <string name="zxing_app_name">Barcode Scanner</string>
    <string name="zxing_button_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="zxing_msg_camera_framework_bug">Sorry, the Android camera encountered a problem. You may need to restart the device.</string>
    <string name="zxing_msg_default_status">Place a barcode inside the viewfinder rectangle to scan it.</string>
</resources>
